Guide to the Candida Scott Piel Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Candida Scott Piel papers
1950-2007
MS 1831
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
22
The Candida Scott Piel Papers document a socially active gay and lesbian culture, centered in New York City, around the turn of the twenty-first century. The papers include subject files, printed materials, writings, ephemera, and audiovisual materials. There is particularly substantive material on AIDS and AIDS treatments, "the circuit" culture, the Jewel Box Revue, and events organized by Piel, mainly as fundraisers for organizations such as the American Foundation for AIDS Research.
Piel, Candida Scott
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Candida Scott Piel, 2004, 2005, 2007, and 2008.
Arrangement
Arranged in five series: I. Subject Files, 1950-2007. II. Writings, 1973-1992. III. Printed Materials, 1950-2003. IV. Memorabilia, 1979-2003. V. Audiovisual, 1959-2002.
Biographical / Historical
Candida Scott Piel was born on May 17, 1952, in New York, New York. She graduated from Yale University in 1974 with a B.A. in Religious Studies. She obtained a Masters Degree in communications from the New York Institute of Technology. After graduating from college, Piel worked briefly in the adult film industry and in gay theater. In 1982, she became involved in Gay Pride Day and chaired the rally in 1984. Piel then became executive director of Friends and Advocates for Individual Rights (FAIRPAC), a political action group. During the 1990s, Piel worked for the American Foundation for AIDS Research (AmFAR) for which she was liaison to the gay community and organized fundraisers and events for AIDS awareness and safe partying. She continues to be active in gay organizations.
Scope and Contents
The Candida Scott Piel Papers document a socially active gay and lesbian culture, centered in New York City, around the turn of the twenty-first century. The papers include subject files, printed materials, writings, ephemera, and audiovisual materials. There is particularly substantive material on AIDS and AIDS treatments, "the circuit" culture, the Jewel Box Revue, and events organized by Piel, mainly as fundraisers for organizations such as the American Foundation for AIDS Research.
Conditions Governing Access
The collection is open for research.
Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy of non-commercially produced items for their personal use should consult the ordering reproductions information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site.
Jewel box revue; AIDS (Disease); AIDS (Disease) -- Treatment; Fund raising; Gay clubs; Gay liberation movement; Gay press publications; Gay Pride Day; Gay theater; Gays and the performing arts; Gays -- Drug use; Homosexuality; Lesbians -- Drug use; Off Off-Broadway theater; Off-Broadway theater; Material culture (genre); LGBTQ resource; Piel, Candida Scott; American Foundation for AIDS Research
- Subject Files, 1950-2007; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  The series is arranged alphabetically by topical headings and contains correspondence, pamphlets, printed materials, photographs, receipts, and other materials. The majority of materials have been left in original folders. When new folders were necessary, headings were taken from original folders. The majority of materials in the series are found under three headings: AIDS/AIDS treatment, "circuit" culture, and Events. "Circuit" culture includes information on "circuit" events as well as the party drugs often associated with them. Events contains materials relating to parties and fundraisers, many of which were organized by Candida Scott Piel. There are three folders of research materials on the Jewel Box Revue.
  - AIDS/AIDS Treatment
    - General, 1988-2002, undated (Box 1, Folder 1 - 4)
    - Alternative medication, nutrition, etc., 1991, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Alternative therapies, 1995, 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Basic research files, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Clinical drug trials, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Clinical trials/ethics, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Combo Cards, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Community resources, 2001-2002, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Disability/work issues, 1997, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Doctor/patient materials, 1993, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Food and Drug Administration, 1997, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Gene therapy, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Hepatitis C, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - HIV and hepatitis C, 1998, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - HIV, etc. treatment, 2000, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Lipodystrophy, 1998-1999 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Medical basics, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Medical information, miscellaneous, 1994-1997 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Medical marijuana, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Medical treatment, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Medicines, miscellaneous, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Medicines, side effects, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - New York Memorial Quilt, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Nutrition/HIV, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Placebos, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - POZ, 2001-2003 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Project Inform, 1994-1995 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Quigong, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Salvage therapy, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Steroids, 2000, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Supplements/vitamins, undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - Treatment information, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Vaccine, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Viral resistance testing, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - Vitamins/herbs/alternatives, 1992, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Vitamins/nutrients, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Wasting, 1998, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Announcements and programs, 1980-2007, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Bible study, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Big Apple Corps, 1987, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Chicago Gay Film Festival, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Christopher Street Liberation Day committee, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - "Circuit" culture
    - General, 1996-2005, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Bad Boy Club Montreal, 1998-2000, undated (Box 3, Folder 47 - 49)
    - Boulder conference, 1999 July (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Club drugs
      - General, 1998-2003, undated (Box 3, Folder 51 - 52)
      - Crystal methamphetamine, 1998, 2002, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
      - Ecstasy, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - GHB/GBL, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Harm reduction, 2002 (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - HX health, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Ketamine, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Viagra and club drugs, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Club Health 2000, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Drug interactions, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Drugs, 1997-1999 (Box 3, Folder 62 - 63)
    - Drugs and harm reduction, undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Drugs in brain, miscellaneous, 1998, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Drugs, sex interrelationship, 2002, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - "Dying to Party, or Partying For Our Lives" [plenary session of a conference], 2002 (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Europe, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Events, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Events listed, 2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - Harm reduction, 1999-2002, undated (Box 4, Folder 71 - 72)
    - Health/party subculture, 1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - MedEvent, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - Medications versus street drugs, 1998-2001 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - Mentions [by Candida Scott Piel through the American Foundation for AIDS Research] on "circuit" sites, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - Morning party, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - National Institute on Drug Abuse, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - New York University conference, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - News articles, 1995, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - News/magazine articles, 1996-2000 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - Parties/drugs, etc., 1998, undated (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - Party drugs, miscellaneous, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - Safe party drugs/GHB, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - Safer parties
      - General, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 85 - 86)
      - Drug policy, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 87)
      - Native Americans/substance dependence, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 88)
      - Producers group, 1997, undated (Box 4, Folder 89)
      - Queer substance (ab)use, drugs/alcohol/cigarettes, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 90)
      - Ravesafe, 2001, undated (Box 4, Folder 91)
    - Sex/drugs/"circuit", 1995-1999 (Box 4, Folder 92 - 93)
    - Shernoff, Michael, "So Many Drugs, So Little Time", 1997 (Box 4, Folder 94)
    - Sociology, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 4, Folder 95)
    - Substance abuse, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Correspondence, 1985-2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Death notices and memorial services, 1988-2002, undated (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Directories, 1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Events
    - General, 1987-2003, undated (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Alchemy
      - General, 1998-2002 (Box 5, Folder 101)
      - Alchemy III promotional and host letter, 2000-2001 (Box 5, Folder 102)
      - Alchemy IV
        - General, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 103)
        - Promotional, 1999-[2002] (Box 5, Folder 104)
      - Blum, Ron [research], 1999 (Box 5, Folder 105)
      - Comments, responses, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 106)
      - Event media clips, 1999-2000 (Box 5, Folder 107)
      - Events, 1999-2001 (Box 5, Folder 108)
      - History, 1998-2000 (Box 5, Folder 109)
      - History and pictures [research], undated (Box 5, Folder 110)
      - Logistics, designs, signs, technology, etc., 1999, undated (Box 5, Folder 111)
      - Pictures, [2002] (Box 5, Folder 112)
      - Slide, undated (Box 5, Folder 113)
    - Dance of the Different Drummer, 1997, 1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Doodads
      - Alchemy, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 115)
      - Bola-6th Avenue, undated (Box 6, Folder 116)
      - Charms/amulets/pendants, undated (Box 6, Folder 117)
      - Decoration and doodads, 1997-1998 (Box 6, Folder 118)
      - Sets, undated (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Druid's Dance, 1999, undated (Box 6, Folder 120 - 121)
    - Event budgets, undated (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Event guidelines, undated (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Event strays, 1998-2000 (Box 6, Folder 124)
  - "Gayspirit, etc.", 2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - I'm Fabulous events, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 126)
    - Novelties, undated (Box 6, Folder 127)
    - Ringwood, New Jersey, Halloween party, 2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 128)
    - Snapper-Bear [Studio], 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 129)
    - Taxes, 1996, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 130 - 131)
    - Trance Dance, 1996-2003, undated (Box 6, Folder 132 - 137)
    - Tribe
      - General, 2000-2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 138 - 139)
      - Ads/art, 2000-2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 140)
      - Background reading/issues, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 141)
      - Doodads, 2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 142)
      - Hosts, undated (Box 6, Folder 143)
      - Medicine wheel, 1994, 2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 144)
      - "My notes", 2002, undated (Box 6, Folder 145)
      - Native American, 1998, 2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 146 - 147)
      - Promotion, 2001, undated (Box 6, Folder 148 - 149)
      - Technology, 1999-2002 (Box 6, Folder 150)
      - 2 Spirit, 1997, 2000, undated (Box 6, Folder 151)
    - 212 postcards, 2001 (Box 6, Folder 152)
    - Venues
      - General, 1998, 2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 153 - 154)
      - Notes
        - Nightclubs-weekly parties, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
        - Offbeat..., 2000 (Box 7, Folder 156)
        - Studios and stages, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 157)
        - Theaters, 2000 (Box 7, Folder 158)
      - Orensanz [The Angel Orensanz Foundation Center for the Arts], 2001 (Box 7, Folder 159)
      - Rand M, 2002, undated (Box 7, Folder 160)
      - Search, 2001, undated (Box 7, Folder 161 - 162)
    - Wicked, 1998, undated (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Fan art
    - General, 1995-1999, undated (Box 7, Folder 164 - 165)
    - How-to plans, 1995, undated (Box 7, Folder 166)
    - McFlags/Ideal World, 1998, undated (Box 7, Folder 167)
    - Media, 1995-2001 (Box 7, Folder 168)
    - Photographs [mainly from clippings or computer printouts], 1997, undated (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Fire Island, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Fundraising for nonprofits; boards; etc., 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Gay and Lesbian Services of Kansas, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 172)
  - Gay Games, 1986, 1994, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Gay media, 1984, 2000, undated (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Heritage of Pride, Inc. [primarily regarding awards ceremony], 1988-1998 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - "I Am" awareness series, undated (Box 8, Folder 176)
  - Identification, business, and miscellaneous cards, undated (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - Jewel Box Club [ Jewel Box Revue; letters of consent, collected materials, research, and photocopies of clippings], 1950-1953, 1983-1984, undated (Box 8, Folder 178 - 180)
  - Johnson, Marsha, memorial, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Lady wrestlers, undated (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Lesbians/feminists, 1979-1981, undated (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Los Angeles Gay/Lesbian Pride Festival, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - New York Feminist Art Institute, 1984 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Penguin sex, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 186)
  - Piel, Candida Scott: autobiographical sketch, undated (Box 8, Folder 186a)
  - Postcards, 1980-2001 (Box 8, Folder 187)
  - Pride conferences, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 188)
  - Pride events, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 189)
  - Royal Short Company, 1986 March (Box 8, Folder 190)
  - The Saint, 1987-1988, undated (Box 8, Folder 191)
  - South Florida Gay Pride Committee, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 192)
  - Spirituality/religion, "God's Gay Tribe", 2002, undated (Box 8, Folder 193)
  - The Sprinkle Salon, 1991, undated (Box 8, Folder 194)
  - Staatts, Tom [Yale College '74], 1991, undated (Box 8, Folder 195)
  - Stickers, undated (Box 8, Folder 196)
  - Stonewall Awards Foundation, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 197)
  - Strengthen the Ties, Break the Chains [Lesbian/Gay Freedom Day Parade and Celebration], 1983 June (Box 8, Folder 198)
  - "Three Dollar Bill", undated (Box 8, Folder 199)
  - Women bodybuilders/wrestlers, 1982, undated (Box 8, Folder 200)
  - Women's Motorcycle Festival, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 201)
  - Miscellaneous, 1980-2000, undated (Box 8, Folder 202)
- Writings, 1973-1992; Series II
  The series is arranged alphabetically and consists of typed manuscripts. Most of the manuscripts are either plays or film scripts, though the series also includes one speech. The actual film of "Inevitable Love" is found in Series V.
  - "Adam and the Experts" [play by Victor Bumbalo], undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - "Beyond AIDS" [speech by Jerry Frankel], 1986 March 29 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - "The Cowgirl and the Blonde" [play or movie script by Jane DeLynn], 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "Dog Heaven" [play by Paul Rudnick], 1992 May 24 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - "Inevitable Love" [with related; movie script by Henry Mach], 1985 August 18 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Jeffrey" [play by Paul Rudnick], 1992 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "Justin and Jack" [play by Neal Weaver], 1973 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Untitled video script [by Joe Smeuyar], undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Printed Materials, 1950-2003; Series III
  The series, primarily arranged alphabetically by title of publication or event, includes magazines, books, clippings, catalogues, programs, posters, and other forms of printed matter.
  - The Advocate [2 issues], 1987, 2001 July 3 (Box 10)
  - "AIDS and HTLV III", 1986 April (Box 10)
  - Airlift Book Company: Women's Complete Catalogue, 1986 (Box 10)
  - Alpha Flight [comic book; vol. 1, no. 106], 1992 March (Box 10)
  - Art and Camera, 1950 November (Box 10)
  - Aurora, 1985 fall (Box 10)
  - Bad Attitude [vol. 1, nos. 1-3; vol. 9, no. 2, 1984 spring-1985 winter, 1994 (Box 10)
  - "Band Notes", 1986 August 9-17 (Box 10)
  - "Beach Book: Rehoboth's Summer Telephone Directory", 1999 (Box 10)
  - "Beyond 2000", 1998/1999 (Box 10)
  - Blueboy [vols. 10-11], 1977 February-May (Box 10)
  - Body Positive [vol. 15, nos. 3-4], 2002 (Box 10)
  - Body Positive HIV/AIDS Resource Directory, 2001 spring (Box 10)
  - "Booked for Brunch?" [vol. 5, no. 3], 1984/1985 (Box 10)
  - The Boudoir Noir, 1993 July (Box 10)
  - The Boys of Taormina [vol. 1], undated (Box 10)
  - La Cage [calendar], 1995 (Box 11)
  - "Camden Womens Voice" [newsletter; issue 4], 1986 July (Box 12)
  - "Celebrating a Decade of S/M Pride" [includes two memorial programs], 1991, undated (Box 12)
  - "Chicago's 15th Annual Gay and Lesbian Pride Week" [souvenir program booklet], 1984 (Box 12)
  - Christopher Street [vol. 2, no. 5; vol. 5, nos. 1, 9], 1977 Nov, 1980 October/Nov, 1981 Sep/October (Box 12)
  - Circuit Noize, 2002 (Box 12)
  - Clippings, 1989, undated (Box 12)
  - Cock Dreams [album 1], undated (Box 12)
  - The Connection, 1983 February 3-17 (Box 12)
  - Craftrends, 2001 May (Box 12)
  - A Decade of S/M Pride, 1991 (Box 12)
  - Detour, 1979 (Box 12)
  - Dyke Sex Calendar 1990, 1989 (Box 12)
  - FAIRPAC [2 issues], 1988 summer, 1990 winter (Box 12)
  - Feel the Pride, Share the Magic, 1983 (Box 12)
  - "Flagging: Propelled by Momentum," Gay and Lesbian Review, 2007 May-June (Box 12)
  - 411, 2001 June (Box 12)
  - The 14th Annual Boston Lesbian and Gay Pride Celebration: Calendar of Events, undated (Box 12)
  - Front Ranger [issue 13], 2000 July (Box 12)
  - GLAAD (Gay and Lesbian Alliance Against Defamation) Newsletter, 1989 fall (Box 12)
  - Gay Community News (GCN) [vol. 22, no. 4; vol. 23, no. 1], 1997 spring-summer (Box 12)
  - "Gay Life" [a special section from The Village Voice ], 1979 June 25 (Box 12)
  - Gay Scotland [no. 28], 1986 Jul/August (Box 12)
  - Gay's the Word Review [no. 41], 1986 June-July (Box 12)
  - Gayellow Pages [3 editions], 1984, 1991, 1997 (Box 13)
  - Girlfriends [vol. 2, no. 2], 1995 Mar/April (Box 13)
  - Greater Gotham Business Council, Inc. Directory [3 editions], 1980, undated (Box 13)
  - Hartford Courant [regarding Yale Alumni Magazine advertisement], 1984 July 21 (Box 13)
  - "Heal Your Body: Metaphysical Causations for Physical Illness" [by Louise L. Hay], 1982 (Box 13)
  - Health and Social Services Referral Guide [New York City Department of Health], 1998 October (Box 13)
  - Health and Venereal Disease Guide for Gay Men [Gay Men's Health Project], 1983 (Box 13)
  - Healthy Living, undated (Box 13)
  - "Hesed V'Emet. AIDS: Our Responsibility as Jews", undated (Box 13)
  - "Hollywood Shore Leave III: The Grand Finale to Benefit A.I.D.S. Action Council", undated (Box 13)
  - Hot Property [no. 7], undated (Box 13)
  - Hot Shots [vol. 10, no. 11], 1995 November (Box 13)
  - "Imperial Court, New York", 1994 (Box 13)
  - Inevitable Love [promotional materials and notebook], 1986 (Box 13)
  - InfoPack [vol. 9, no. 3], 1999 (Box 13)
  - Jewel Box Revue [program], 1958 September 25 (Box 13)
  - "Jewelry for Exotic Piercings", 1997 (Box 13)
  - Junger Apoll, undated (Box 13)
  - "Last Summer at Bluefish Cove" [play program], undated (Box 13)
  - "Leather Pride Night '96", 1996 June 22 (Box 13)
  - "The Lesbian and Gay Big Apple Corps Symphonic Band, Swing Band, Marching Band" [vol. 1], undated (Box 13)
  - Lesbian and Gay Film Festival [program], 1982 March 4-27 (Box 13)
  - "Lesbian Herstory Archives" [newsletter; nos. 8-10, 15], 1984 winter, 1986 Sep, 1988 Feb, 1995 January (Box 13)
  - "Lesbian Poetry", undated (Box 13)
  - Let Freedom Ring, 1987 October 10 (Box 13)
  - Life Ball, undated (Box 13)
  - Male Athletic Nudist [vol. 1, no. 4], 1968 (Box 14)
  - The Male Figure Review [no. 1], 1969 (Box 14)
  - Male Masturbation, undated (Box 14)
  - The Manhandlers [no. 3], 1979 (Box 14)
  - Manual of American Nudists [no. 1], undated (Box 14)
  - Metro Weekly [vol. 7, no. 48], 2001 April 5 (Box 14)
  - MetroSource, 2002 Dec/2003 January (Box 14)
  - "Michael's Thing" [no. 10, vol. 16], 1986 March 6 (Box 14)
  - "The Mr. Altar", undated (Box 14)
  - "Mr. Leather New York", 1995 (Box 14)
  - "The Names Project" [program], 1988 (Box 14)
  - The National Gay [no. 32], 1986 July 8 (Box 14)
  - National Film Theatre, 1987 Oct/November (Box 14)
  - "A New Gay Dawning" [Gay Pride Festival souvenir program], 1982 (Box 14)
  - New York [article on the play "One Mo' Time"], 1980 August 4 (Box 14)
  - New York City Pride Guide 2002 (Box 14)
  - New York City Tribune [vol. 4, no. 91], 1986 May 8 (Box 14)
  - New York Native [issues 38, 263], 1982 May 24-June 6, 1988 May 2 (Box 14)
  - New York Newsday, 1989 June 8 (Box 14)
  - "New York Pride Guide" [circular to request advertising], 1999 (Box 14)
  - Newsweek [vol. 119, no. 8], 1992 February 24 (Box 14)
  - Next [The Official Heritage of Pride Rally Guide; vol. 7, issue 48], 2000 June 9 (Box 14)
  - Night of 100 Parties [FAIRPAC], 1989 (Box 14)
  - Night of a Thousand Gowns, 1990 (Box 14)
  - The 1980 Clone Calendar (Box 14)
  - The 1981 Gay Pride Festival (Box 14)
  - NYQ [no. 18], 1992 March 1 (Box 14)
  - The Official Heritage of Pride Lesbian and Gay Pride Souvenir Program, 1993 June 26 (Box 14)
  - Official Pride Events Guide 2000 (Box 14)
  - Official Souvenir Program, 1984 (Box 14)
  - On Our Backs [vol. 3, no. 4; vol. 9, no. 3], 1987 spring, 1993 Jan/February (Box 15)
  - "Open Your Eyes" [posters], 1985 (Box 15)
  - Oriental Trading Company, Inc. catalogue, 1999 (Box 15)
  - Other Stages [vol. 2, no. 20], 1980 June 12-25 (Box 15)
  - Out Front, 2000 (Box 15)
  - Out/Look [vol. 1, nos. 1-3; vol. 2, nos. 2, 4; vol. 3, no. 2; no. 11], 1988-1991 (Box 15)
  - Outrageous Women [vol. 1, nos. 2-4; vol. 2, nos. 1, 3; vol. 3, no. 2], 1984-1987 (Box 15)
  - Outweek [no. 47], 1990 May 23 (Box 15)
  - The Physical Man [no. 6], undated (Box 15)
  - Pink Pages, 1997 winter/spring (Box 15)
  - Playboy [vol. 25, no. 5], 1978 May (Box 15)
  - Posters
    - General [Climax; Columbus, Ohio; Gay Pride; Rites; Barnum & Bailey; Richard Sabala; Alchemy; gay film; Seeds; Brentford Watermans Arts Centre; Street Theater: Christopher Street the Night of the Stonewall Riots; the Saint: Black Party, Last Party], 1984-2002, undated (Box 16)
    - The Saint at Large, 1982, 1988-1994, 2004, undated (Box 17)
  - "The Power Exchange" [vol. 1, nos. 1-3], 1984 Jun, Sep, 1985 January (Box 18)
  - Prejudice and Pride, 1988 June (Box 18)
  - Pride Guide, 1983 (Box 18)
  - Prostitutes of New York Press newsletter [vol. 1, no. 1], 1989 (Box 18)
  - QW [no. 28], 1992 May 10 (Box 18)
  - "Read this Before Coming Out to Your Parents", 1984 (Box 18)
  - "Royal Short Company News" [vol. 4], 1986 spring (Box 18)
  - Run No More, 1972 (Box 18)
  - San Francisco Gay Life [nos. 1, 4], 1977 (Box 19)
  - Sappho: The Art of Loving Women, 1975 (Box 19)
  - Sappho by the Sea, 1976 (Box 19)
  - "Saturday, October 11. No Time Like the Present.", 2003 (Box 19)
  - Die schwulen Buchläden [no. 4], 1990 (Box 19)
  - Scientific Workshop on Lesbian Health 2000 (Box 19)
  - The Search for Signs of Intelligent Life in the Universe [program], undated (Box 19)
  - Soho News, 1980 June 25-July 1 (Box 19)
  - SpeakOUT [vol. 1, no. 3], 2000 summer (Box 19)
  - Stars [vol. 5, issue 3], 1991 May (Box 19)
  - Stormy Leather catalogue, undated (Box 19)
  - Substance Abuse Resource Guide, 2000 (Box 19)
  - Swirl [issue 5], undated (Box 19)
  - Tales of the Closet... [no. 2], 1987 fall (Box 19)
  - Tapestry Journal [issue 69], 1994 fall (Box 19)
  - 10 Percent [vol. 2, no. 7], 1994 Mar/April (Box 19)
  - Tender Buttons [vol. 1, no. 1], 1985 spring (Box 19)
  - "3 Dollar Bill", 1990 October (Box 19)